<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">ParkAware</string>

    <string name="home"></string>


    <string name="warning_title">Welcome to the ParkAware Community</string>
    <string name="warning_subtitle">Helping you park smarter and avoid unnecessary fines.</string>
    <string name="warning_legal">Remember to drive and park legally and safely and always be respectful of others.</string>
    <string name="warning_cta">Let’s Park Smart</string>
    <string name="warning_did_you_know">Did You Know?</string>
    <string name="warning_privacy">ParkAware Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="warning_eula">Apple EULA</string>

    <string name="profile_title">User Profile</string>
    <string name="profile_avatar">Avatar</string>
    <string name="profile_change_avatar">Change Avatar</string>
    <string name="profile_section_account">Account</string>
    <string name="profile_user_name">User Name</string>
    <string name="profile_user_id_fmt">User ID: %1$s</string>
    <string name="profile_sub_free">Subscription: Free</string>
    <string name="profile_sub_pro">Subscription: Pro</string>
    <string name="profile_sign_out">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="profile_delete_account">Delete Account</string>
    <string name="profile_upgrade_to_pro">Upgrade to Pro</string>
    <string name="profile_restore_purchases">Restore Purchases</string>
    <string name="profile_name_error">Name must be at least 2 characters</string>
    <string name="profile_guest">Guest</string>
    <string name="profile_not_signed_in">Not signed in</string>
    <string name="profile_delete_title">Delete Account?</string>
    <string name="profile_delete_msg">This action is permanent and will delete your account and local data.</string>
    <string name="profile_recent_login_title">Sign in again required</string>
    <string name="profile_recent_login_msg">Please sign in again to confirm account deletion.</string>
    <string name="profile_delete_failed_title">Couldn’t delete account</string>
    <string name="profile_delete_failed_msg">Please try again later.</string>

    <string name="report_officer">Parking Officer / Ranger</string>
    <string name="report_chalk">Tyres Chalked</string>
    <string name="report_fine">Fine Issued</string>
    <string name="my_location">My location</string>

    <string name="sd_report">Report</string>
    <string name="sd_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="reminder_scheduled_ok">Reminder scheduled</string>
    <string name="reminder_title">Parking Reminder</string>
    <string name="reminder_body">Your parking time is nearly up. Head back to your car.</string>
    <string name="reminder_channel_name">Parking Reminders</string>
    <string name="reminder_channel_desc">Notifications to remind you before parking expires.</string>

    <!-- Reminders / FAB -->
    <string name="set_reminder">Set parking reminder</string>

    <!-- Reminders screen -->
    <string name="reminders_title">Parking Reminders</string>
    <string name="rem_scheduled_fmt">Reminder set for %1$d minutes (alerts 5 min early)</string>
    <string name="rem_cleared">All reminders cleared</string>
    <string name="rem_enable">Enable Smart Parking Reminders</string>
    <string name="rem_default_time">Default Reminder Time</string>
    <string name="rem_minutes_hint">Minutes (e.g. 30)</string>

    <string name="rem_style">Notification Style</string>
    <string name="rem_style_hint">Choose how reminders appear</string>

    <string name="rem_set_now">Set reminder now</string>
    <string name="rem_clear_all">Clear all scheduled reminders</string>

    <string name="rem_info">
    Smart Reminders can prompt you to set a timer after you park.
    You’ll be alerted 5 minutes before your selected time.
</string>

    <string-array name="warning_tips">
        <item>Many cities tow during street cleaning hours even if signs are faded—double-check the schedule.</item>
        <item>Temporary construction signs often override regular rules. Scan the whole block before you park.</item>
        <item>Pay-by-phone zones can still ticket if you’re outside the zone code—verify the number on the sign.</item>
        <item>Time limits reset after posted end times; overnight often has different rules.</item>
        <item>Check both sides of the street—restrictions can alternate by day or time.</item>
    </string-array>

<string name="about_body"><![CDATA[
ParkAware is about bringing the community together to raise awareness of safety issues around parking and other parking related issues that impact our lives every day, through education and transparent and respectful reporting.

How It Works
• Share sightings of parking enforcement officers (respectfully)
• Get parking reminders and location alerts
• Stay informed about council-related activity

Founded in 2025
Contact: admin@parkaware.app
]]></string>

<string name="disclaimer_body"><![CDATA[
Last Updated: 01/07/2025

ParkAware is a community-driven application developed to promote parking awareness, encourage safe and lawful behaviour, and help users stay informed about parking restrictions, enforcement presence, and related council matters.

By using ParkAware, you acknowledge and agree to the following:

1. Informational Purposes Only
The content and alerts provided by ParkAware are offered for general informational purposes only. They are not intended to be, nor should they be considered, professional advice or legally binding instructions.
You remain fully responsible for complying with all applicable parking laws, signage, and local government regulations.

2. No Guarantee of Accuracy
While we aim to provide up-to-date and relevant information, ParkAware may rely on user-submitted, third-party, or publicly available data and cannot guarantee accuracy or timeliness.

3. No Liability for Fines or Incidents
ParkAware is not liable for parking infringements, towing, damage, or losses resulting from parking decisions or use of the App.

4. Respectful Conduct
Any use of the App to incite or support abuse, threats, or harassment toward Police Officers, Council Rangers, or Parking Officers is strictly prohibited.

5. No Use While Driving
Do not interact with the App while driving.

6. Changes and Updates
This Disclaimer may be updated at any time without notice.

7. Contact
Use the feedback form on the Contact Us screen.
]]></string>

<string name="terms_body"><![CDATA[
Effective Date: 01/07/2025

Welcome to ParkAware (“we”, “us”, “our”). These Terms & Conditions (“Terms”) govern your use of the ParkAware mobile application (“the App”) and any related services we provide. By downloading, accessing, or using the App, you agree to be bound by these Terms and our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree, please do not use the App.

1. Purpose of the App
• Promote awareness of local parking rules
• Help users stay informed about potential fines, restrictions, and enforcement activity
• Encourage safe, respectful, and lawful behaviour

2. Community Standards
Users must not submit false or misleading information, incite abuse/harassment, or promote hostility toward enforcement personnel.

3. User Responsibilities
Follow all laws, treat information as general guidance, take personal responsibility for your actions, and do not use the App while driving.

4. Accuracy of Information
We do not guarantee accuracy, completeness, or reliability. Always verify important information with your local authority.

5. Purchases, Trials & Subscriptions
Subscriptions may auto-renew unless cancelled in your store account settings. We do not store your payment details.

6. Data Privacy
We collect and process personal data per our Privacy Policy. You can delete your account at any time; some data may be retained as required by law.

7. Limitation of Liability
The App is provided “as is” without warranties of any kind.

8. Intellectual Property
All content and trademarks remain the property of the developers.

9. Changes
We may update these Terms at any time.

10. Termination
We may suspend or terminate access for violations.

11. Governing Law
New South Wales, Australia.

12. Contact
admin@parkaware.app
]]></string>

<string name="privacy_body"><![CDATA[
Effective Date: 01/07/2025

ParkAware (“we,” “our,” or “us”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, and share information when you use our mobile application (“App”).

1. Information We Collect
• Account info (name, email, sign-in)
• Subscription/purchase info
• Device info and crash reports
• Location data (when permission granted)
• Optional user content

2. In‑App Purchases, Free Trials & Subscriptions
Handled securely through the app store; manage in your account settings.

3. Account Deletion
You can delete your account in User Settings. Some anonymized data may be retained for legitimate purposes.

4. How We Use Information
Provide/improve the App, manage accounts/subscriptions, send necessary notifications, ensure security.

5. Sharing
No sale of personal data. Limited sharing with providers, for legal reasons, or in business transfers.

6. Your Choices
Update info, revoke location, delete account, manage subscriptions.

7. Data Security
We use appropriate safeguards, but no method is 100% secure.

8. Changes
We may update this policy from time to time.

9. Contact Us
admin@parkaware.app
]]></string>

    <!-- Settings -->
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Sign in -->
    <string name="signin_subtitle">Choose how you’d like to sign in</string>
    <string name="signin_google">Sign in with Google</string>
    <string name="signin_guest">Continue as Guest</string>
    <string name="signin_failed_google">Google sign-in failed. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="signin_failed_anon">Couldn’t continue as guest. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="parking_education">Parking Education</string>
    <string name="education_header">ParkAware Education</string>
    <string name="filter_sightings">Filter Sightings</string>
    <string name="report_sighting">Report a Sighting</string>
    <string name="set_parking_reminder">Set a Parking Reminder</string>
</resources>